Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, Residence Division, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, Residence Division, records
1938-1973
1960-1971
SC0121
Stanford University. Office of the Dean of Student Affairs. Residence Division.
20 Linear feet
The collection consists of correspondence, memoranda and other material relating to both the physical management and the social and educational value of student living groups.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Dean of Students Office, Residence Division, 1974.
Information about Access
Restricted: for more information see the archivist.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Residence Division has charge of all administrative matters relating to Stanford dormitories, row houses, fraternities, sororities and eating clubs.
Description of the Collection
The collection consists of correspondence, memoranda and other material relating to both the physical management and the social and educational value of student living groups.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Office of the Dean of Student Affairs. Residence Division.; Dormitories--California--Stanford.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Alumni Association, 1961-1966 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1966-1970 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Clubs, A-M, 1955-1968 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Clubs, N-P, 1958-1967 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Clubs, Q-Z, 1958-1968 (Box 1)
  - Alumni College, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Complaints, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Conferences and Programs, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report - Director, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report - Director, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report (Draft form), 1972 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: General, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: Policies and Function, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: Registered Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: Social Action, 1962-1964 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: Social Procedures, 1963 (Box 1)
  - ASSU: Student Review Board, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Associated Women Students Board, 1962-1966 (Box 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Committee on, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
  - Business Office, 1965-1968 (Box 1)
  - Counseling and Testing, 1957-1965 (Box 1)
  - Campus Religious Programs, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - Century 21, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Civil Defense, 1963-1967 (Box 1)
  - Co-ed Housing, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
  - Co-ed Symposium, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Conferences, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Conferences on World Youth Movements, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: General, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Directors, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Cowell Health Center, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Dean of Men, 1950-1965 (Box 2)
  - Dean of Women, 1946-1965 (Box 2)
  - Dedication, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Development, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Director-Expense Reports, Program Allowance, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Director's Meetings Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - Director's Meetings Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Director's Meetings Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Director's Meetings Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Director of Residence's Office, 1960-1965 (Box 2)
  - Discrimination, 1957-1967 (Box 2)
  - Encina Commons Dining Room, 1965-1969 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Advisors, 1960-1967 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Master's Program, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Residents, 1961-1964 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Residents, 1965-1969 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Residents, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Residents in Women's Residences, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Fallout Shelter Committee, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Federal Housing Loan, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Financial Aid Policies, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Fire Safety, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Firearms, 1964-1969 (Box 2)
  - Food Complaints, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Food Service, 1966-1970 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Student Associate Program, 1965-1968 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Student Housing, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Students and Visitors, 1962-1966 (Box 2)
  - Form Letters, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Achievement Awards, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Alumni Achievement Awards, Personal Statements of Activities, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Guest Meal Ticket Plan, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Housing Assignments, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Program: Surveys, Proposals, Etc., 1957-1964 (Box 2)
  - Freshman Voices, 1966-1967? (Box 2)
  - Fundamental Standard and Honor Code, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Funk, Robert, and Dogs, 1968 (Box 2)
  - General Secretary, 1951-1965 (Box 2)
  - General Secretary, 1966 Jan-Aug (Box 2)
  - General Secretary, 1966 Sep-Dec (Box 3)
  - General Secretary, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - General Secretary, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Grade Point Averages, 1952-1968 (Box 3)
  - Grade Point Averages - Residence, 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Coordinating Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Guest-in-Residence Program, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - High School Day, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Horton: Copies of Dorm Interviews, Undated (Box 3)
  - "House Plan" at Stanford, 1960-1964 (Box 3)
  - Housing (Office) General, 1947-1968 (Box 3)
  - Housing, 1963-1967 (Box 3)
  - Housing, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Housing, 1968 Autumn (Box 3)
  - Housing, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Food Service Committee Minutes, 1959-1964 (Box 3)
  - Housing Commission and Ideas, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Housing Commission Report, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Housing Configuration Committee, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Housing Contract Releases, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing Deposit Refund Cards, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Housing Draw, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing: Graduate, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Housing: Innovations, Proposals, Etc., 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Housing: Married Student, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing: Overseas Students, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing Problems, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Housing Survey-S. Bushnell, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Housing Survey Material, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Information for Faculty Residents and Directors, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
  - Inquiries: General, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Job Description, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Lighting Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 3)
  - Long-Range Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Married Undergraduates-Study, 1966 Fall (Box 4)
  - Meal Exchange Program, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Meal Transfer Evaluation, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Memorandums to Residence Directors, 1965-1968 (Box 4)
  - Minorities, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1970 (Box 4)
  - Occupancy Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - OFF, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - OFF, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Open House-Changes, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
  - Open House Policy, 1963-1968 (Box 4)
  - Operating Committee Proposal, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Overnight Guest Policy in Women's Residences, 1962-1968 (Box 4)
  - Overnight Policy, History of, 1962-1967 (Box 4)
  - Overseas Campuses Housing, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Police Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Policy Statements and Reports on Housing, 1957-1962 (Box 4)
  - Pot, 1968-1971 (Box 4)
  - President's Short-Range Housing Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Director, 1962-1963 Fall (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Director, 1963-1964 Fall (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Director, 1964-1965 Fall (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Resident Assistants, 1963-1964 Fall (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Resident Assistants, 1963-1964 Spring (Box 4)
  - Quarterly Report, Resident Assistants, 1964-1965 Fall (Box 4)
  - Quarter Reports, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Questionnaire on University Living for Undergraduate Women, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Reports on Housing, Research, Etc., 1962-1966 (Box 4)
  - Research, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Residence Budgets, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
  - Residence Configuration, 1970-1972 (Box 4)
  - Residence Halls-10 Year/5 Year Programs, 1960-1965 (Box 4)
  - Residence Interviews, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Residence Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Residence Recommendations: History, 1959-1969 (Box 4)
  - Residence Renovations, 1959-1969 (Box 4)
  - Residence Staff Study, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Residence System, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Residences, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - Residences Background, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Residences, Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 5)
  - Residences-Plans-Men, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Residences-Plans-Women, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Residences: Trailer Housing, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistant Program, 1962-1967 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistants' Analysis, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistant Orientation, 1961-1965 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistant Orientation-Men's and Women's, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistant Orientation, 1965-1968 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistant Orientation, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistants, 1968-1972 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistants, Suggestions made by, 1962-1971 (Box 5)
  - Resident Assistantships, Posters for, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Residential Education Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
  - Residential Education Program, Inquiries, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
  - "Safe Place", 1970 (Box 5)
  - Security, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Senior Weekend, 1958-1966 (Box 5)
  - Short-range Housing Committee, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Social Counselor's Annual Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Social Regulations, 1960-1967 (Box 5)
  - Social Regulations, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Sororities, 1938-1953 (Box 5)
  - Special Houses, Programs, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Sponsor Programs and Suggestions, 1962-1966 (Box 5)
  - Sponsoring at Wilbur Hall (notebook), 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Sponsoring at Wilbur Hall (notebook), 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Sponsors, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
  - Sponsors, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Sponsors' Handbook, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Staff Orientation Evaluation, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Staff with Dual Appointments, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
  - Staffing, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Teacher Education Program (STEP) and Student Center for Innovation in Research and Education (SCIRE), 1970 (Box 6)
  - State Housing Act, 1964-1968 (Box 6)
  - Student Associate Program, 1964-1970 (Box 6)
  - Strike, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Strike-Dean of Students Information, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Student-Faculty Employment Committee Petitions, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
  - Student Health, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
  - Study of Education at Stanford, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Study of Education at Stanford, Report, 1968 Fall (Box 6)
  - Summer Housing, 1965-1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Quarter, 1959-1967 (Box 6)
  - Summer Resident Assistants, 1961-1968 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, Florence Moore, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: American Field Service Reunion, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Budgets, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Cancellations, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Catapult farce, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Cultural Events, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Expenses, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Food Service, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: High School Debate Institute, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Jobs, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Master Lists, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Memos from Dean of Students, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Memos to Resident Assistants, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Movies, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Requests, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Room and Board Bills, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Room and Board Changes, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Security Patrol, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Social Program, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Staff, Correspondence for, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Students, Correspondence with, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Summer Session: Sunday Film Series, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Task Force, 1967-1971 (Box 6)
  - Theme Housing, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
  - Traffic Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Vacation Housing: History, 1961-1967 (Box 6)
  - Vending Machines, 1965-1967 (Box 6)
  - Year End Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Branner Hall: General, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Branner Hall: Film Workshop, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Branner Hall: Miscellaneous, 1961-1968 (Box 7)
  - Brennan, Patrick, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Crothers Hall, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Crothers and Crothers Memorial, 1967-1970 (Box 7)
  - Crothers Memorial, 1970 Summer (Box 7)
  - Demonstration Houses, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Durand House, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Ecology House (Experimental House Summer), 1970 (Box 7)
  - Environmental House Room Requests: Females, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Environmental House Room Requests: Males, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Escondido and Crothers, 1970 Summer (Box 7)
  - Escondido Village-General, 1959-1965 (Box 7)
  - Escondido Village (and High Rise Units), 1959-1966 (Box 7)
  - Escondido Village High Rise Apartments, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Florence Moore Hall, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Florence Moore Hall: Personal Statement, 1961-1969 (Box 7)
  - Florence Moore Hall: Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Florence Moore Hall: Student Night Assistants, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Grove House (The Row), 1968 (Box 7)
  - Grove Project, 1966-1969 (Box 7)
  - Hoskins House-High Rise Apartments, 1964-1968 (Box 7)
  - Hoskins House Resident Assistants, Wright, Mr. and Mrs. R. Michael, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Hulme House, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - International Houses, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Lagunita Court, 1963-1969 (Box 7)
  - Lagunita Court, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
  - Lagunita Court: Summer Session, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Lasuen Houses and Tamarack Lodge: Residences Survey, 1957-1960 (Box 7)
  - McFarland House: Williams, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - McLennan, Melodie, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Manzanita Lodge, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Manzanita Park, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Mayfield House, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Moore/Jacks Houses-Planning, 1961-1967 (Box 7)
  - Riggs, David R. and Susan, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall, 1965-1970 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall: Head Sponsor and President Reports, 1963 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall: Minority Housing, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall: Miscellaneous, 1961-1968 (Box 8)
  - Roble Hall: Night Assistant, Adele Adams, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - The Row, 1964-1970 (Box 8)
  - The Row: Discipline, 1962-1964 (Box 8)
  - The Row: Miscellaneous, 1961-1969 (Box 8)
  - Science Fiction House, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Stanford Village Dormitories, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
  - Stanford Village Rosters, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
  - Stern Hall, 1957-1960 (Box 8)
  - Stern Hall, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
  - Stern Hall, 1963-1966 (Box 8)
  - Stern Hall, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Stern Houses, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Donner House, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Fremont House, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Stern Freshmen Coordinators, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Grove Demonstration House, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Holladay House, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Lassen House, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Stern: Serra House, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall and Eating Clubs, 1961-1969 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall and Eating Clubs, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall and Eating Clubs, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall: Director Glenn S. Hara, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall: Resident Dr. Stanley Fischman, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Toyon Hall: Secretary, Mrs. Bernice Watson, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur Hall: General, 1956-1967 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur Hall: Head Sponsor Reports [Encina Hall freshman sponsor reports included before 1956], 1951-1962 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur Hall: Housekeeping, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur Houses: General, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur: Otero Demonstration (International), 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur: Record, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur: Soto Demonstration House (Creativity), 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur: Summer, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Wilbur: Trancos House, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Fraternities: Accounts Receivable, 1969-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Address List, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Advisory Council, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Conference, 1967-1972 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Conference, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Corporation Officers, 1964-1970 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Alumni Relations, 1968-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Annual Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Auditing, 1962-1966 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Background Information, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Bid Card Procedure, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Bilateral Movement, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Boarders, Placement and Transfers, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Complaints, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Conferences, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Establishment Dates, 1068 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Expansion, 1952-1968 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Finances, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Forum, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General, 1961-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: General Problems, 1968-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: House Managers, 1962-1968 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: House Presidents, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Housing Development, 1956-1961 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Housing Policy, 1962-1968 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Inquiries about Housing, 1960-1967 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Interfraternity Board (IFB) and Interfraternity Council (IFC), Composite File, 1963-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFB, 1949-1967 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFB, 1960-1967 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFB, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFB, Minutes, 1960-1965 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Interfraternity Constitution, 1959-1963 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC, 1946-1956 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC, 1957-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC, 1963-1969 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC, 1968-1972 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC Judicial Council, 1963-1965 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC Judicial Council, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: IFC Minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities: Libraries and Librarians, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Meal Exchange Program, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: National Intrafraternity Conferences, 1966-1969 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Non-Cluster, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Non-Cluster Policy, 1967-1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Non-Cluster Policy, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Other Nationals - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Pledge Lists, 1961-1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Pledge Lists, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Procedures for Going Local, Undated (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Program Allowance, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: "Proposal for Change and Development of the S.U. Fraternity System;" New Policy Statement: Results, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Questionnaire Results, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Report on Stanford Fraternity System, 1955-1969 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Residents' Personal Problems, 1961-1966 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Resident Assistants, 1963-1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rosters, 1964-1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rosters, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1965-1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush Booklets, 1962-1970 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rushbook, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Fall Rush for Freshman and Transfers, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Greek Week Activities, 1959-1969 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Regulations and General Inquiries, 1965-1969 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Reorganization, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Rules, 1954-1960 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, Rules, 1960-1967 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Rush, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fraternities: Spring Meeting, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Staffing, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Summer, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Tax Exemption-Gifts, 1955-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Use of for conferences, etc., other than summer, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Western Regional Interfraternity Council, 1964-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Workshop Fall Quarter, 1969-1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Clusters: Discussions of New Clusters, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Clusters: Rental, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Clusters, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster I, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster I, Bill Leland, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster II, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster II, John E. Hanson, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, Deke and Chi Psi Move to Row, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, Bob Freelen, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, Letters to Neighbors, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Cluster III, Public Relations, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Delta Phi, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Delta Phi, 1968-1972 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Kappa Lambda (History Only), 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Phi Omega, 1952-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Sigma Phi, 1955-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Sigma Phi, 1956-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Sigma Phi, 1962-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omega Building Association Minutes, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omicron, 1959-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omicron, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omicron, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omicron, Discrimination Matter, 1957-1961 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Chi, 1962-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Chi, 1963-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Chi, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Chi, Probation and Receivership, 1958-1965 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Chi's Woe (Institute of Non-Violence), 1969 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Theta Pi, 1952-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Theta Pi, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Theta Pi, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Beta Theta Pi, Requests for Course Incompletes (Typhoid Cases), 1967 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Chi Psi, 1952-1968 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Chi Psi, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Chi Psi, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities: Delta Chi, 1948-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Chi, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Chi, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1952-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1967-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Tau Delta, 1960-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Tau Delta, 1964-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Tau Delta, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Tau Delta, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Upsilon, 1952-1967 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Upsilon, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Delta Upsilon, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Alpha, 1952-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Alpha, 1967-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Alpha, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Sigma, 1952-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Sigma, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Sigma, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, 1952-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, 1966-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, 1970-1971 (Box 12)